RG 002:025, Committee on Contested Elections
Connecticut State Library
Committee on Contested Elections records
1985
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut. General Assembly. House of Representatives. Committee on Contested Elections
.25 cubic feet
Meeting minutes, transcripts, and report related to Gloria Bogen, Republican Candidate for office of State Representative in the 73rd Assembly District, challenge of the results of the November 6, 1984 election and the recanvas thereof.
RG002_025_CONTELEC
T001600
Scope and Content
Meeting minutes, transcripts, and report related to Gloria Bogen, Republican Candidate for office of State Representative in the 73rd Assembly District, challenge of the results of the November 6, 1984 election and the recanvas thereof.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Connecticut. General Assembly. House of Representatives. Committee on Contested Elections -- Records and correspondence; Contested elections -- Connecticut
Document Types:
Minutes; Transcripts; Reports
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1985
  - Statement of challenge, 1985 January 11 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, 1985 January 10 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Meeting transcript, 1985 January 10 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Meeting transcript, 1985 January 11 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Meeting transcript, 1985 January 16 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Meeting transcript, 1985 January 18 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Meeting transcript, 1985 January 22 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Meeting transcript, 1985 January 23 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Transcript of the House of Representatives session, 1985 January 24 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Report of the Committee on Contested Elections, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 10)